nationalcherryblossomfestival.org 2018-02-02

# Privacy Policy - National Cherry Blossom Festival

### Content and Information

All Content is the responsibility of the Content provider, and we are not responsible or liable for the Content provided by others. Some Content may be protected by intellectual property rights owned by others who provide Content to us. Unless we permit you in writing, you may not copy, sell, trade, use or allow others to use the Content.

You are responsible for the information that you provide to us about yourself (“Information”) and for the consequences of providing us with that Information.

### What Information we gather

You decide how much of your Information you disclose to us and to the independent entities Constant Contact, Yahoo! or PayPal (“Affiliates”) who collect information on our behalf.

If you want to receive email updates about the Festival (“Updates”), you will provide to Constant Contact your name, e-mail address, and zip code (“Subscriber Information”). The Constant Contact policy regarding this Subscriber Information is at

<http://ui.constantcontact.com/roving/CCPrivacyPolicy.jsp>. Constant Contact will not provide the Subscriber Information to us, but may provide us with demographic statistics about those who opt in to receive Updates.

If you place an order for Festival merchandise at our Website, you will provide to Yahoo! the item or items you are ordering, your payment information, including your name, mailing address and phone number, billing address, e-mail address and credit card information (“Purchaser Information”). The Yahoo! privacy policy regarding this Purchase Information is at <http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/security/details.html>. Yahoo! does not provide the Purchaser Information to us, but only your name, mailing address and the item or items you ordered (“Order Information”) so that we may fulfill your order. Yahoo! may also provide us with general order demographic information, which we may use to design future merchandise programs.

If you donate to the Festival, you will provide to PayPal your payment information, including your name, mailing address and phone number, billing address, e-mail address and credit card information (“Donor Information”). The PayPal privacy policy regarding this Donation Information is at [https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US](https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US). PayPal will not provide the Donation Information to us, but only your name, contact information and the amount that you donated (“Donation Information”).

You are responsible for the accuracy of the Information that you provide. You may correct and update your Information at any time by contacting us or, as appropriate, our Affiliates. We periodically audit the Information that we receive and will remove information that is incomplete or which you have informed us is inaccurate.

We may gather and archive basic Website logging statistics showing the daily number of visitors to our Website and its subdirectories, daily requests for particular files, originating server locations and server or browser domain names. We use these aggregated statistics internally to provide better services, but we may also provide these statistics to others.

### What Information we do not gather

We do not gather non-public personal information such as your Social Security number or any other information that could be used to determine credit- or employment-worthiness.

### Where we and our Affiliates gather Information

We and our Affiliates gather Information from you in plainly-marked areas of our Website. For example, we request Information from you when you:

  * Sign up for Updates from us.
  * Place an order for Festival merchandise.
  * Donate to the Festival.

### How we use Information

We may use Information to:

  * Help us to know our visitors.
  * Enable us to enhance your Website visit, and to improve and customize the content and layout of our Website and other communications tools.
  * Track usage of the Website.
  * Send to you Updates to which you have subscribed.

### How we share Information

We do not sell, share or trade your Information to third parties. We may share Information with sponsors in the form of non-personalized, demographic information. Our Affiliates may share Information, subject to their own privacy policies.

If we or our Affiliates are required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Information, we or our Affiliates will do so to the extent that we determine disclosure is appropriate. We or our Affiliates may also provide Information as necessary to protect the personal safety of the public.

### How we store and send Information

We maintain security procedures and standards for storing and sending Information which we believe are as safe as today’s technology permits. We test these procedures and modify them regularly as new technologies become feasible.

We do not store or send your personal Subscriber Information. Constant Contact will store your Subscriber Information on its servers, subject to its own privacy policy, until you unsubscribe via email or by contacting us.

We do not store or send Purchaser Information. We will store Order Information only for as long as it takes us to fulfill the order, and then we will destroy all Order Information. Yahoo! will store the Purchaser Information, subject to its own privacy policy, only for as long as it takes us to fulfill the order and allow for returns or exchanges, and then Yahoo! will destroy all Purchaser Information except your email address for the purpose of tracking and Yahoo! strategic marketing (“Yahoo! Marketing”).

PayPal will store Donor Information, subject to its own privacy policy, only for so long as it takes to process the donation. We store but do not send Donation Information. We may use Donation Information to send you receipts for tax purposes and for future donation solicitations (“Future Solicitations”).

### Opting Out

If you do not want to receive Updates, Yahoo! Marketing, or Future Solicitations, you can opt out in several ways:

  * Click on the opt-out link provided in an Update.
  * Email us at ncbf@downtowndc.org requesting that you name be removed from future Updates, Yahoo! Marketing or Future Solicitations.

Write us at 1275 K Street, NW, Suite 1000, Washington, DC 20005, requesting that you name be removed from future Updates, Yahoo! Marketing or Future Solicitations.

### Other Websites

The Website may contain hyperlinks to other websites, content or resources (collectively, “Other Sites”). Other Sites may gather information about you when you view them. We cannot control their collection of information and suggest that you review Other Sites’ privacy policies before providing them with your personal information.
